下面就是你们上周错过的内容
This is what you missed last week on Shameless.
全是关于哥的 非常的酷炫
It was great. It was all about me.
差不多就是一趟英雄的旅程
Sort of the hero's journey.
-我在哪  - 华瑞兹（墨西哥城市）
- Where am I? - Juarez.
我错过圣诞了么
Did I miss Christmas?
你都快错过复活节了
You almost missed Easter.
- 早上好 Debs  -都137天了 爸爸还没回来
- Morning, Debs. - 137 days.
他会回来的 Debs 他总是会回来的
He'll be back, Debs. He always comes back.
- 你好啊 Steve -嘿 Nando
- Well, hello, Steve. - Nando.
我没想过会在这能看到你
You know, I was surprised to see you in the States
我以为你会在缉毒局的监视名单上
'cause I-I thought that the DEA had you on a watch list.
我确实在
They do.
所以你能想到 我有多高兴能过来吧
So you can imagine how happy I am to come here.
我已经给Estefania买了一张芝加哥大学经济学证书
I've arranged for Estefania to pursue an economics degree.
我想让她成为一个美国公民 Steve
I want her to be an American citizen, Steve.
所以 当移民局过来调查时 你就是她的合法丈夫
When Immigration comes, you will be her husband.
这也就意味着 你不能再惹麻烦了
But that means you can't get into any trouble.
那我怎么活啊
How am I supposed to make a living?
找个工作
Get a job.
我今天把工作丢了
Lost my job today.
我们付产权税的钱够么
We gonna have enough for the property tax bill?
只要加上我今天领的支票就行了
Just, with the check I got today.
Lip和Ian早走了
Lip and Ian left early?
他们说上学之前他们要去市中心
They said they had to pick something up
去取个什么东西
downtown before school.
- 去市中心 -他们就是这么说的
- Downtown? - What they said.
我希望你给我机会尝试做一下助理经理
I was hoping you'd give me a shot at assistant managing,
就像我们去年秋天商量好的那样
like we discussed last fall.
给我1000块 我就给你安排一晚上试试
Give me 1,000 bucks, I'll find you a night to promote.
1000块 全在这儿了
$1,000. It's all there.
那好吧 你来试试吧
Okay. You're on the calendar.
-天哪 -嘿 你能把那个递给我
- Oh, my God. - Hey, can you pass me that--
- 老爸
- Daddy!
无耻之徒字幕组呈现
♪ think of all the luck
you got ♪
翻译 子健 我爱大胖神 荷叶杯 塞林
♪ know that
it's not for naught ♪
翻译 波娜娜 拉比少少 kernalson 胡小贼
♪ you were beaming
once before ♪
校对 胡小贼 子健 dream
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
后制  赖布
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of♪
♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so sure of♪
♪
♪ round up the friends
you got ♪
♪ know that
they're not for naught ♪
♪ you were willing
once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of♪
♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
无耻之徒字幕组 倾情呈现
♪ you're so sure of♪
♪
我槽
Shit!
怎么了
What's the matter?
那可是1000块钱啊
$1,000.
-快继续睡吧 -我都不能呼吸了
- Mm, back to sleep. - I can't breathe.
可能是因为你把枕头摁在脸上吧
Maybe it has something to do with the pillow on your face.
我要去付产权税
I gotta pay the property tax.
好吧好吧 快点过来
All right, come here,come here, come here.
别用那玩艺戳我
Stop poking me with that thing.
我以为你喜欢我用这玩艺戳你呢
Thought you liked me poking you with this thing.
我当时是怎么了
What was I thinking?
你是因为那个夜店的事不爽么
Is this about the club thing?
我做了个噩梦
I woke up having a panic attack
我感觉我就像是Frank和 Monica那样 顺走我们的钱
that I was just like Frank and Monica taking our money,
唯一的区别是 我甚至都没让自己嗨一下
except I wasn't even getting high with it.
你一定会举办一个酷炫的夜店之夜的
You know, you're gonna throw a kick-ass club night.
你想成为一个不一样的人吧
You gotta be entrepreneurial, right?
那你就要投资你自己
Invest in yourself.
你现在是在大便吗
Are you taking a dump right now?
- 每天早上 准的像闹钟一样 - 我的天
- Like clockwork, every morning. - Jesus.
干嘛 我都不能在这大便吗
What, I can't take a dump in here?
不能当着我的面拉啊
Not in front of me you can't.
但是你在浴室里啊
You were in the shower.
对啊 但我现在出来了
Yeah, and now I'm out of the shower.
你要是在我面前拉大便我不会介意啊
I wouldn't care if you took a dump in front of me.
唉
Ugh.
草 怎么回事
Oh! What's going on?
Frank醉了 在找床
Frank drunk looking for a bed.
谁他妈的让他来找床的
Who the hell let him?
-是Debbie -我们都求过她别这样了
- Debbie! - We begged her not to.
-我不会让他睡我的床的
- He's not hot-bunking my bed.
他干嘛不能就睡在外面沙发上 那里够暖和了
Why can't he sleep out on the porch? It's warm enough.
我要睡回我原来的床
I want my old bed back.
该死 不行
Oh, hell, no!
过来吧 爸爸 上来
Come on, daddy. Up.
小心台阶
Step, step.
早上好 Frank
Morning, Frank.
这可是我的房子
This is my house!
没关系的 爸爸 你可以睡在我的房间里
It's okay, daddy. You can sleep in my room.
不行啊 Debs
Wouldn't do it, Debs.
他今早特别臭
He's especially ripe this morning.
Frank闻起来像狗尿一样
Frank smells like dog piss.
才不是狗尿
Not dog piss!
—流浪汉Gary才是  —过来吧老爸
- Gary the homeless guy. - Come on, daddy.
祝你好梦啊 爸爸
Sweet dreams, daddy.
嘿 那可是我的帐篷
Hey, that's my tent.
等他醒了我会帮你把它冲干净的
I'll hose it off after he wakes up.
Debs 别让Frank再进来了
Debs, don't let Frank in here anymore.
这也是他的家啊
This is his home too.
他可是消失了几个月
He disappeared for months.
但他现在回来了 借过
And now he's back. Excuse.
买牛奶的钱
Milk money.
你的早饭
Breakfast.
你拉屎之后洗干净了没
Did you wash up after you pooped?
你以为你是我妈吗
What are you, my mom now?
拉屎之后 我们应该要洗手的吗
We're supposed to wash up after we poop?
让你女朋友穿好衣服 Lip
Tell your girlfriend to wear clothes, Lip.
我又不是他爸妈
Not her keeper.
你不想看就别看啊
Don't look if you don't like what you see.
真是好臀
Sweet.
快穿裤子 现在就穿
Pants. Now.
老天
Jesus.
嘿 你今天去上学吗
Hey, you going to school today?
噢不 晚点去吧 前三节课我得翘了
Oh, no. Later. Gotta skip my first three periods,
我得去做社工了
so I can start clocking community service hours.
补齐产权税的最后50块 哟
And the last 50 bucks to the property tax, yo.
钱这样差不多能够
This should bring us right around where we need to be.
我还没把我上次清理有毒废料挣来的钱
I didn't put in the money from that last
-放进去  -好吧 没问题
- toxic waste gig I had yet. - Okay, that's cool.
把那些钱拿过来
Hand it over, and I'll drop it off
我去做社工的路上顺便去把税给交了
before I go to community service, pay the tax man.
不在我手上了
I don't have it.
-什么东西不在你手上了 -那些钱
- Don't have what? -The money.
我用那些钱去交夜店的包夜保证金了
I used it to put down a deposit on a club night.
行了
All right.
Debs Carl 我们走吧 该去上学了
Debs, Carl, let's go. School time.
我要先去给爸爸送早饭
Gotta bring daddy his breakfast first.
但是产权税已经拖了两个星期了啊
Uh, but the property tax, that's already two weeks late.
我们总要拖两个星期的
We're always two weeks late.
party之后我会把钱拿回来的
I'll have the money back right after the party.
那些钱又不是你能随便花的
It wasn't yours to spend.
我能啊 都是我挣的
Yeah, it was. I earned it.
噢 原来我们现在都能这么干了啊
Oh. Oh, that's how we're doing this now.
那行啊 我要把我上周挣的钱拿出来
Okay, well, I'll take the money I made last week
去买个Ipad
and buy an iPad.
Ian 你支票上的钱准备怎么花
Ian, what are you gonna do with your paycheck, huh?
去买个新的皮夹克 Liam呢
New leather jacket? Liam?
我现在有个机会能好好挣些钱 Lip
I have an opportunity to make some real money here, Lip.
这个机会很难得的
It's not that easy.
我已经做了很久的夜总会生意了
I've been in the club business a long time.
对啊 你是做了 那只是送送鸡尾酒好吗
Yeah, sure you have.Slinging cocktails, okay?
听着 你根本就不懂怎么筹划夜总会party
Look, you don't know shit about promoting a club party.
谢谢你给我鼓劲 Lip
Thanks for the vote of confidence, Lip.
♪ I'm a working man
with a 9:00 to 5:00 ♪
嘿 老爸 给你带来了早饭哦
Hey, daddy.Brought you breakfast.
♪ Gotta be a slave ♪
还有报纸
And the newspaper.
你回家了真好
Good to have you home.
你能帮我完成我的社会学习课题吗
Can you help me with my social studies project?
是关于内战的
It's on the Civil War.
我要做一个林肯的小木屋
Gotta build Lincoln's log cabin.
-Debs  -嗯
- Deb. - Hmm?
太吵了 我需要安静
Too much noise. I need peace and quiet.
我正要睡觉
I'm trying to sleep.
真的假的啊 你居然要送我到路边
Seriously? You're walking me to the curb?
怎么 难道我回到过去 变回了6岁了吗
What, did I go back in time and turn six?
在学校好好学习啊 Carl
Have a good day at school, Carl.
学些有用的东西回来
♪ we called it love ♪
♪ but even the sun sets
in paradise ♪
♪ I'm at a payphone
trying to call home ♪
Payphone - Maroon 5
♪ all of my change I spent on you ♪
♪ where have the times gone♪
魔力红乐队
♪ baby it's all wrong ♪
♪ where are the plans we made for two♪
你也喜欢 Maroon 5
You like? Maroon 5.
你他妈在这里干嘛啊
What the hell are you doing here?
你找到工作了没
Have you gotten a job yet?
-还没 -Nando都跟你说了要你找工作的
- No. - Nando told you to get a job.
听着 我不知道巴西形势现在怎么样
Listen, I don't know what it's like in Brazil,
但我们现在可在经济衰退期
but we're in a recession here.
噢 这样啊
Oh. Hmm.
我会从现在开始看着你的
I'll keep my eye on you from now on, okay?
什么
Excuse me?
确保你不再惹上什么麻烦
Make sure you don't get into trouble.
我们现在是搭档了
We are partners now.
你去哪 我也去哪
Wherever you go, I go.
就像夫妻一样
Like a married couple, huh?
♪ Even the sun sets in paradise ♪
♪ I'm at a payphone ♪
兄弟 他们干嘛叫你来干这个
Why they got you doing this, man?
B E 因为我偷窃 伤人
"B" and "E," theft, and assault.
-不错  -你呢
- Nice. - You?
用板砖打了一小屁孩的脸 让他有点破相了
Hit a kid with a brick. Kinda broke his face.
那你为那事罚了多少个小时啊
Hey, how many hours you get for that?
五十
50.
我槽 我被罚了120
Shit, man, I got 120.
至少这里总有人带着大麻
Least there's always someone with some weed.
嘿 有大麻吗
Hey, got any weed?
10块一支
10 bucks a joint.
看 我说的吧
See, what'd I tell you?
那群低级的搓人是怎么回事
What's up with the geek squad?
那他妈的是 欢乐合唱员 的演员么
Is that the fucking cast of Glee?
是的 看起来像一帮做善事的人
Yeah. Looks like a bunch of do-gooders.
更像一帮想被揍扁的人
More like a bunch of gonna get their ass kicked-ers.
♪ Back in high school ♪
♪ when I really liked you ♪
♪ I was always just a friend ♪
嘿 Meg
Hey, Meg.
嘿 怎么样
Hey. What's up?
我想要一份你的员工表
Wanted to get your staff list.
好主意 当然了
Oh, yeah, sure. That's a good idea.
我还想知道我们能不能重新商量一下我的分成
Was also wondering if we could renegotiate my split of the bar.
你不接受15％
15% doesn't work for you?
我听说Wandell得了 差不多30％
I heard Wendell gets, like, 30%.
他是我最好的承办人
He's my best promoter.
他能带来一大批人
He brings in,like, a huge crowd.
这还是你第一次 办这个需要时间锻炼的
It's your first gig. It takes time.
如果她自己带酒来呢
What if she brought her own booze?
我们可以从Kev那里弄到酒
We'll get it from Kev.
就能赚到更多钱 那会好办多了
Make more money, it'll work out better.
你们承办时挣的钱 要和我在的时候挣的一样多哦
Gonna have to make it worth my while.
我们可以还是这么分钱
We could do the same split,
只是我拿85％ 你拿15％
except I keep the 85% and give you the 15%.
行啊 你自己带酒来
Okay.Bring your own booze.
可我要20％
But I want 20%.
♪ Tattooed in my mind just like a memory ♪
♪ when I looked in your eyes ♪
♪ You call me, I call you ♪
♪ I see you every day at school ♪
爽
Yeah.
用力啊
Come on, GI.
像对待伊拉克士兵一样捅我
Pound me like an Iraqi soldier.
行了 你他妈给我闭嘴
Okay, you need to shut the fuck up.
不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
你还在说话
Still talking.
哎 下面怎么回事
Hey!What's going on under there?
- 操  －谁啊
- Fuck, fuck. - Who is it?
可能是老师 或者是什么垃圾
Probably a teacher or some shit.
你跟你说了 你叫的太大声了
I told you you were too loud.
听着 我不能被开除 我爸妈会杀了我
Look, I can't get expelled. My parents will kill me.
可能听说了搞基这事 他们会先震惊死
Probably hearing about the gay sex will kill 'em sooner.
看我撞见了什么好事
Lookee what we got here.
Mickey?
我以为你还在少管所里
Thought you were still in juvie.
现在不在了啊
Not anymore.
你在这下面做着某种奇特的爱呢
You having some sort of queer-bo sex under here?
没 我发誓
No, no, I swear.
你怎么只揍我啊 他也做了啊
Why are you still beating me up? He was doing it too.
你是菊花被插的那个 对吧
You're the one taking it in the ass, right?
所以你是我要痛扁的那个
You're the one I gotta kick straight.
你懂了么
It working?
-懂了懂了 -好
- Yes, yes. - Good.
滚出去
Get the hell outta here.
你还有精力做么
You got any fuck left in you,
还是已经把力气全耗在那废柴菊花里了
or you dump it all in that faggot's ass?
噢 我的小 奇奇
Oh, my little chee-chee.
拜托不要哭了
Please don't cry.
拜托不要哭了 我亲爱的小宝贝
Please don't cry, my little boy.
拜托别哭了
Please don't cry.
妈妈好累啊
Mama's so tired.
你都不想休息休息你的小肺肺么
Don't you want to give your wee lungs a--
啊
Aah!
啊啊啊
Aah.
妈呀 太吵了
Oh, God, that's so loud.
什么东西都吵
Everything's so loud.
一会回去让Jody给你揉揉肚子
Maybe when we go inside, Jody can rub your tummy.
然后妈妈能睡一会会
And mama, she can take a little nap.
Karen小时候可没有你这么闹人 Hymie
I don't remember Karen causing such a fuss as you, Hymie.
可能你是从天朝人那继承的
Maybe it's from your Chinese side.
好啦
Okay.
挺好的 你让Hymie安静了
Cool, you got Hymie
to quiet down?
Hymie
Hymie!
不要
No!
不要 不要 不要 他不是垃圾
No! No, no, no, he's not trash!
他不是垃圾
He's not trash!
Hymie!
我的妈呀
Oh! Oh, my God! Oh, my-- oh, my--
太对不起了
I'm so sorry!
没事 Sheila 他挺好的
It's okay, Sheila, he's fine.
他差点被卡车装走
No, but he was almost swallowed up by the truck!
我不是个称职的妈妈
Oh, my-- I'm such a terrible mother.
没有 你就太困了
No, you're just--you're just a tired mother.
我都不配活着了
I don't deserve to live.
-起来吧，回屋里  -我真是太
- Come on, let's go back inside. - I'm such a t-- No.
我们叫Debbie来照看
We'll call Debbie to come baby-sit again,
我们也能休息休息
and we'll get some rest.
-好吗 起来吧  -对不起
- Okay? Come on. - I'm sorry, baby.
-好啦  -没有 没有
- It's okay. - No, no, no!
你没抽过大麻吗
You ever shoot crack?
没有
No.
吃过毒碱蘑菇吗
Ever eat mescaline-laced mushrooms?
也没有
Nope.
龙舌兰泡卫生巾塞屁股里
Put a tequila-soaked tampon up your ass?
啥 没整过 哥们儿
What? No, dude.
我知道了 我明显没有你牛
I get it. I'm-- I'm obviously not as cool as you.
好香啊
Smells good.
必须的 一等货
Yeah, it's, um, primo stuff.
20块钱一根
20 bucks a joint.
5块行吗
Can I buy five?
当然
Yeah, sure thing.
我是Casper
I'm Casper.
- Lip. - Grizz.
你住附近？
You live around here?
大概4个街区
About four blocks over.
不错
Cool.
是啊
I guess.
你呢
Where you from?
莱克肖尔
Uh, Lakeshore.
没办法 我在那出生的
I didn't choose it,I was just born there.
你在这做啥？体验穷苦生活
What are you doing，slumming it down here?
城市青年
City Youth.
美化芝加哥 一次一个街区
We're, uh, beautifying Chicago one block at a time.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
那些花活不过两个小时
Those flowers-- they're not gonna last about two hours.
干这个只是想让我申请塔夫茨大学的简历好看点
Just looks good on my tufts application.
招生办的人让我来你们这扶贫帮困
Admissions people are into you helping out the poor and shit.
对不起
Oh, sorry.
没事
It's okay.
没关系
I'm not offended.
你想美化
you interested in beautifying
附近其他地方吗？
any other parts of the neighborhood?
能让我简历厉害 干啥都行
Anything to beef up my CV.
我想到一个地方适合你
Think I may have something for you.
我看看能不能搞到
See if I can work it out.
哥们 随时联系我
Dude, hit me up anytime.
我在Facebook上 Casper Duncan
I'm on Facebook. Casper Duncan.
记住了 Casper Duncan
You got it, Casper Duncan.
真爽啊 哥们
Man, that was good.
想你了
Missed ya.
是吗
You did?
可不嘛
Yeah, man.
在少管所里我得当小攻
I had to do all the fucking in juvie.
不然就得任人摆布 对吧
Otherwise I'd end up someone's bitch, right?
回来真爽
Nice to switch back.
以为你还有四个月呢
Thought you had four more months.
可能是因为没床位了 才放我出来的
Yeah, let me out for overcrowding or some shit.
回来接着上课吗
Coming back to school?
必须不是啊 我还得从九年级开始
Hell, no, man. I'd still be a fuckin' freshman.
一门考试都没过
I haven't passed a single class.
那你干嘛回来
Why'd you come back, then?
进去之前买了一堆可卡因
Fronted a bunch of coke before I went in.
现在拿回去
Time to collect.
爽爆了
That's good.
爽
So good.
一个女的这周打三个电话了 Kev
Third call this week from that same woman, Kev.
-她没留言吗  -没有
- She won't leave a message? - No.
可能就是个买发票的
Probably a fucking bill collector.
你就别管她了
Can you just keep dodging her, please?
亲爱的 脚怎么样了
Hi, baby. How's the foot?
痒死爷了
It's goddamn itchy.
你们俩狐狸精干啥来了
What are you two foxy ladies up to?
从你这整点酒
Need to bum some liquor off ya.
给她的夜店
For her club night.
什么 他们那没有酒吗？
What, they don't have booze over there?
自己带酒赚的更多
She'll make more money if she brings her own.
行吧 瘸过来
All right. Hobble this way.
你要多少
Okay, how much you need?
这些不够
More than this.
至少要200人 宝贝
There's gonna be at least 200 people there, babe.
你什么时候见过我这一次来
Have you ever seen more than 20 deadbeats
超过20个大仙
in here at one time?
那你批发商呢
What about your liquor distributor?
从他那进货咋样
Could I get the booze from them?
可能也行
Yeah, maybe.
对于Roselli来说，Walter是个好人
Walter's a cool enough guy, for a Roselli.
啥？你还跟黑道有联系呢 咋没告诉我呢
What? You're dealing with the mob? You never told me that.
没人喜欢Stan
Stan burned every bridge in town.
Walter是唯一愿意
Walter's the only liquor distributor
卖给我们酒的
that'll do business with us.
酒水大概要多少钱
How much would the booze cost?
200人 纯酒 差不多5千
For 200 people? Top shelf? Close to 5 grand.
加饮料调酒的话，差不多3千
For well drinks, you'd probably get away with 3.
他能让我赊账吗
Would he let me set up an account and invoice me later?
可能行 但他会做信用调查
Yeah, maybe. He'll do a credit check, though.
我信用贼好
I've got perfect credit.
没有信用记录不等于就是好
No credit does not equal perfect credit.
你有社保号吗
Do you even have a social security number?
他可能会要一个孩子做抵押
He'll want you to leave one of the kids as collateral.
好 我明白了
Okay, I get it.
那我就跟他直接结账
I'll just buy the booze from him up front, then.
你用谁的钱结账
Whose money you gonna use?
真烦人
Douche bag.
服装售货员
Uniform sales.
大巴司机
Bus driver.
小炒厨师
Short order cook.
-哈喽哇，吉米米  -你回来啦
- How's it going, Jim-nasium? - Hey, what's going on?
能借我点银子吗
Can I borrow some money from you?
必须的 要多少
Yeah, sure, how much?
5000 从夜店回来还你
$5,000? Pay you back after my club night?
咋的
What?
是啊 手头有点紧
Yeah, kinda strapped right now.
我身上有300
I got, like, uh, 300 bucks on me.
那是我的牛仔裤吗 Frank
Are those my jeans, Frank?
在我屋里看见的
Found 'em upstairs in my room.
那已经不是你的屋了
It's not your room anymore.
你要把她的裤子剪成短裤吗
You're cutting her jeans into shorts?
我以前有三条 被别人扔没了
Had three pair of my own, but somebody tossed my clothes.
这裤子差不多120块钱
These are, like, $120.
我在二手店买的40块
I got 'em at Goodwill for, like, 40 bucks!
你去银行再取点钱呗？
Can you go to the bank and get more money?
我没有了
I don't have any.
你父母那呢
What about your parents?
我18岁之后他们啥也不给我了
I haven't gotten anything from them since I was 18.
-真的吗 学费呢  -车呢 保险呢
- Really? College? - Cars, insurance.
好吧 我是从18岁就没有跟家里要过现金了
Okay, I haven't gotten any cash from them since I was 18.
两年来你一直要给我钱
For two years you've been offering to give me money,
现在我跟你要 你反而没有
and now when I ask, you don't have any?
我真没办法
I'm sorry.
这就是为什么我不找别人帮忙
This is why I never ask anybody for help.
-我觉得自己像个混蛋  -你在生我的气
- I feel like a jackass now. - Whoa, hey. Are you mad at me?
我给你钱的时候  你生我的气
Because you get mad at me when I offer you money,
现在我没法给你钱，你也生我气
and now you're getting mad because I can't?
我自己解决 好了吧
I'll just figure it out myself, okay?
我们走吧 v
Let's go, V.
Frank 搞啥呢
Frank, what the hell?
烤鸡是今晚的晚饭呢
I got that roast chicken for dinner tonight!
这是我的家 我的厨房 我的冰箱 我的鸡
My house, my kitchen, my fridge, my chicken.
裤子剪太短了 我的蛋蛋都快露出来了
I cut these too short. My balls are hanging out.
屁股不错呀
Nice ass.
还以为你是历史老师Crouch先生呢
Thought you were my history teacher Mr. Crouch.
不好意思 让你失望了
Well, sorry to disappoint.
社区服务怎么样
Hey, how was Community Service?
挺好的
Yeah, good.
我遇到了一群北区的孩子
I met some North Side kids.
应该能从他们身上赚一笔
Think I can make some dough off 'em.
那不错
Cool.
我得尽力补足
Yeah, gotta do what I can
老姐从物业税中拿走的钱
with my sister stealing a bunch of our property tax money.
她真狡猾
Well, that was cunty of her.
其实应该你来管你家的钱
You know, you should be in charge of your family's money,
而不是Fiona
not Fiona.
Mr. Gallagher 我刚从Mr. Healey的办公室离开
Mr. Gallagher,just left Mr. Healey's office.
你们俩的谣言是真的
Rumors about you two true?
他说你想跟我要推荐信吗
Said you were supposed to ask me for a recommendation.
对 他觉得我应该这么做
Sure, in his mind, I was supposed to do that.
一封理科老师的推荐信
A letter of recommendation from a science teacher
对你的大学申请很有帮助的
looks good on your college applications.
我猜是
Bet it does.
我们现在有20箱啤酒 16箱葡萄酒
So we got 20 cases of beer,16 cases of wine,
还有两箱香槟
got two cases of champagne.
我有10升伏特加 6升琴酒 4升朗姆
I got 10 liters of vodka, six gin, four rum,
4升威士忌，4升波旁，足够的混料器和鸡尾酒橄榄，
four scotch, four bourbon, and enough mixers and garnishes
大概够200个人份的
for, like, 200 people.
-真的吗  -是的
- Sound about right?
- Yup.
要是我没用完  可以退 对吗
And I can return whatever I don't use?
没错
Absolutely.
我来帮你记清楚
Let me just tally this up here for you.
你搞什么呢
What are you doing?
预定酒啊 你以为呢
Ordering booze. What's it look like?
最好别让我卖身还债啊
I hope the payment doesn't involve my titties.
算好了 亲爱的 一共是 4857刀
Okay, my dear, I got you in at $4,857,
因为你是kev的朋友 给你打九折
which includes the 10% discount 'cause you're a friend of Kev's.
因为你是第一次买
And I went ahead and waived the delivery fee
送货费也给你免了
'cause you're a first-time customer.
你打算怎么付钱
How would you like to pay for this?
-支票  -需要笔吗
- Check. - Need a pen?
谢谢
Yes, please.
让我看看我的行程
Let me go check the schedule,
看看什么时候能给你送去
see what time we'll get this out to you, okay?
好的
Mm-hmm.
-稍等一下  -咋了
- 'Scuse me. - Yes.
那个账户里就只有17刀吧
Is there more than $17 in that account?
等到支票兑现的时候  我就有钱了
By the time the check clears, I'll have it covered.
这个男的是混黑帮的
The guy is in the mob.
你就凭Kev的名头给他开空头支票
You' cutting him a check trading on Kev's good name?
做人要敢想敢干
Gotta be entrepreneurial,right?
如果我不投资我自己 没人会的
If I don't invest in myself, no one else ever will.
请进
Come in.
真是稀客啊
Oh, surprised to see you
你怎么会来学校咨询中心 Miss Milkovich
at the college counseling center, Miss Milkovich.
我是来跟你讨论lip的
Came to talk to you about Lip.
我不应该跟你讨论别的学生
I'm not at liberty to discuss another student,
我更愿意
but I'd be more than happy to help you
讨论你的前程
with your future options.
算了吧
Please.
我们都知道 我唯一的前途
You and I both know my only options
就是被搞大肚子 要不就是被抓起来
are getting pregnant or getting arrested,
所以就别废话了
so cut the crap.
好的
Okay.
那就说说lip吧
Then Lip.
他有个很好的机会  可以离开这
He's got a good chance of getting out of here.
那你能帮他什么呢
And what are you doing about it?
鼓励他去上大学
Encouraging him to go to college.
但他好像不是很有兴趣
Doesn't seem to be too interested.
你是个辅导员 就他妈指导他啊
You're a guidance counselor. Fucking guide him.
我能做的是有限的
There's only so much I can do.
-他该怎么办  -一直保持高分
- What should he be doing? - Keeping his grades up.
拿到老师的推荐信
Getting teacher recommendations,
做点应该干的事
finding himself a legitimate job,
把他的大学申请写好
filling out his college applications.
你觉得你能帮着吗
Now, you think you can help with any of that?
也许吧
Maybe.
好吧 晚些时候来我这趟
All right, stop by at the end of the day,
我会弄一些大学的宣传册
I'll post some college brochures,
你可以拿点
you could take 'em with you.
我觉得你比我
I think you have a better chance
更能说通他 吕西斯忒拉忒
of getting through to him than I did, Lysistrata.
什么
What?
偶尔来上趟英语课
Show up for English once in a while,
我会给你写推荐信的
and you'll get the reference.
好的
All right.
来，小家伙
Let's go, buddy.
好的
All right.
我还没黑到也没有醉到成你老爸
No, I'm not black enough or drunk enough to be your daddy.
你真的要我去哪 就跟到哪吗
You seriously gonna keep following me everywhere I go?
这是我的工作
It's my job.
难道你都不用去卫生间
Don't you ever have to go to the bathroom?
好吧
Okay.
好吧 liam 我们走
Okay, Liam. There you go.
Este 是我
Hey, Este, it's me.
为什么你喘的这么厉害
Why are you breathing so hard?
我健身呢
Gym.
你真是让人猜不到
You never know with you.
Beto正在我家门口
So Beto is sitting out front.
我去哪他跟到哪
He follows me wherever I go.
是你爸让他监视着我的么
Your father told him to keep an eye on me?
-不用担心  -他没想干什么  -谁
- Don't worry. He's harmless. - Who?
你爸还是Beto
Your father or Beto?
他俩可都不像是善茬
Because neither of them seemed harmless
特别是他俩锯开Marco的时候
when they were dicing up Marco.
啤酒 我要喝啤酒
Beer. I need beer.
等会 Frank
Just a second, Frank.
别惹事 你就没事的
Stay out of trouble, and you'll be fine.
听着 我得走了
All right, listen.I gotta go.
我有点事要办 得给Fiona攒点钱
I gotta run some errands, make some money for Fiona.
我老爸是个急脾气
Look, my dad is a hothead.
常常一下就发很大的火  吓我们
Blows off steam, threatens lives,
然后不生气了 也忘了他为什么生气
and then cools down, forgets why he was mad.
他肯定是双子座的
He is gemini.
他很快就会让Beto离开的
He will call Beto off soon.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Gracias.
打扰下
Hey, uh, 'scuse me.
那些呆在这的瘾君子去哪了
What happened to all the meth heads squatting in here?
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
热心的街坊
Concerned neighborhood citizen.
我花了6个月才摆脱他们
Took me six months to get rid of 'em.
我听说里面有死人
Yeah, I heard there were dead bodies in there too.
有 4个 还有一阵野狼来吃那些尸体呢
Yeah. Four, yeah. Coyotes got to 'em at one point.
这房子估计得收拾8周  才能重新住人
Gonna take me eight weeks to make it livable again.
你付这些人多少钱
How much you paying these guys?
挺多的
Too much.
也许你可以省点钱
Might have a better deal for you.
-意面怎么样  -挺好吃的
- How's the pasta? - Good.
你现在就像我们的女仆
You're like our maid now.
谢谢你 Carl
Thanks, Carl.
Debs 能看会liam吗
Hey, Debs,watch Liam for a bit.
-我要去办点事  -不行
- I gotta run an errand.- No can do.
-得帮Sheila看小孩  -Carl
- Baby-sitting for Sheila. - Carl.
我能熬夜看电视吗
Can I stay up late and watch TV?
当然
Absolutely.
我今晚要去Sheila家 老爸
I'm going to Sheila's tonight, daddy.
我要去那看孩子
Baby-sitting.
这个工作不错 Debs
A noble job, Debs.
那个小破孩还在哭
That stupid baby's still crying?
不带停的
Won't stop.
嘿 那是我的牙刷
Hey, that's my toothbrush.
谢谢你的慷慨  儿子
And thanks for sharing it with me, son.
-天啊  -现在我们又是一家了
- Oh, man, eew! - Now that we're a family again,
我想鼓励大家 人人为我 我为人人
I want to encourage us to be all for one and one for all.
现在得煮它去消毒
Ew, gonna have to boil it now.
你需要Sheila家的电话号码吗
You need the number over at Sheila's?
我等会去那
Where I'll be.
不用 为什么要
No, why would I?
我一会就去Alibi了
I'll be heading out
to the Alibi soon.
不用担心 我大晚上一个人走回来
Oh, and don't worry about me walking home late at night.
我在枕头套里放了挺多的肥皂
I have a pillowcase full of bars of soap.
干的好
Good for you.
不要光说好听的
You get along a lot better
你还得带上点硬家伙 这样才行
with a weapon and a kind word
than a kind word alone.
意面还有剩吗
Any of that spaghetti left?
真是的
Oh, darn it.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
不让Frank进来
Keeping Frank out.
想去卡耐基梅隆大学么
Planning to go to Carnegie Mellon?
拜托
Please.
书呆子和同性恋才去那
That's for nerds and homos.
但是Healey认为lip应该申请那
But, um, Healey thinks Lip should apply.
估计没戏
Fat chance.
他那么聪明
He's smart enough.
却非要让这些都白白浪费
Yeah, but too stupid
to do anything about it.
我已经试过了
I already tried.
我能问你个问题吗
Hey, can I ask you a question?
问
Sure.
你怎么知道
How do you know if a guy
一直跟你在一起的男的是不是喜欢你
you've been hanging out with likes you?
你喜欢他嘛
You like him?
嗯 但我觉得他讨厌我
Uh-huh,
but I think he hates me.
你去问问他吧
Ask him.
他根本不想谈
Doesn't want to talk about it.
没有男的想谈这个
No guy ever does.
那你怎么知道呢
How do I know, then?
你和他在一起时 他有那种眼神吗
Does he get that look in his eye when he's with you?
什么眼神
What look?
你看到就知道了
You'll know when you see it.
你知道亚当林肯生的时候
Did you know that Abe Lincoln lived in a one-room log cabin
是住在一个小木屋吗 Hymie
when he was born, Hymie,
而且他的祖父被印第安人偷袭杀害了
and that his grandfather was ambushed and killed by indians?
有些历史学家说他对女性很冷淡，
Some historians say that because he was cold to women,
可能是因为他有同性恋倾向
he might've had homosexual tendencies.
你看会Hymie
The whole point of you baby-sitting Hymie
让他安静点 我和Jody睡会觉
was to keep him quiet, so Jody and I could get some sleep.
不好意思 Sheila 但是他一直哭
Sorry, Sheila, he won't stop.
要不你带他出去溜溜
Why don't you take him for a walk?
-去哪  -无所谓
- Where? - I don't care.
随便哪
Just anywhere.
过几个小时再回来
Just don't come back for a few hours.
行吗
Okay?
咋了
Hey, what's up?
你在哪呢
Hey, where are you?
我
I am...
去办事了
running an errand.
你在哪呢
Where are you?
在V家 换衣服呢
Uh, at V's, changing.
我要去趟Club 谈谈这次主题活动的事
I'm gonna run by the club,talk to this promoter.
看看能不能弄到他的联系名单
See if we can get his email list
找更多的人来
to invite more people to my party.
好主意
Good idea.
你能看着孩子吗
You mind watching the kids?
好的
Got it covered.
谢了 回见
- Thanks. Bye.
我出来了，出来了
Okay, okay, okay, I'm out.I'm out, I'm out.
你为什么偷保时捷
Why you steal Porsche?
我需要钱帮我的女朋友
I needed money to help my girlfriend.
你家里不就有辆车吗 卖了它就可以了
You have a car at home. Sell that.
那我怎么出门
How am I supposed to get around?
你要是惹麻烦的话 Nando会杀了我们两的
Nando will kill us both if you get into trouble.
好吧 我发誓再也不干了 好吧
Okay, I promise not to do it again, okay?
你背叛了我
You betray me.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
应该是断了
Clean break, I think.
别再惹我了
Don't screw with me again.
知道了
Fine. Okay.
走吧
Come on.
我带你去医院
I take you to the hospital,
然后后去吃个美式大汉堡咋样
then we go get American Whoppers, huh?
♪ You've got it ♪
♪ the way
you grinding up on me ♪
♪ I know, I know you want me ♪
♪ the way
you kissing up on me ♪
♪ I know, I know you need me ♪
Wendell在么
Hey, Meg, is Wendell around?
在那边
Uh, yeah, right over there.
♪ The way
you grinding up on me ♪
谢了
Thanks.
我告诉你
I'll tell you this.
除了太懒和没有上进心意外
For all of their laziness
and lack of motivation,
墨西哥人其实挺不赖
Mexicans are a lovely people.
你为啥去了那
Why'd you go down there, Frank?
再给我一瓶
Hey, I'll take another, Kev.
有时候男人就该得出去走走
Sometimes a manj ust has to get away,
和思想一同踏上孤旅
be alone with his thoughts.
然后酒醒一觉
So what, you woke up from a drunken stupor,
不知身在何方
didn't know where you were?
我一直知道我在哪
I knew exactly where I was.
在那是因为
Had a business opportunity
和我的南疆兄弟们有笔生意
with our south-of-the-border brothers.
- 你脚怎么了  -摔了一下
- What did you do to your foot? - It fell off.
我就能付得起这破玩意
Was the only prosthetic I could afford.
什么好生意啊
What kind of business opportunity?
雇我送批货
I was hired to move some inventory.
毒骡子啊
Drug mule?
我是他们墨西哥人见过的最棒的一个
Only the best the mexicanos have ever seen.
Frank 这可不是什么光宗耀祖的事
Not something you really want to be bragging about, Frank.
-你是在哪头装的啊
- Which end did it go in?
有个带着孩子的小妞在外面找你
Some chick's outside with a baby looking for you.
-这是谁啊  -我 我不知道
- Who is it, Frank? - I-I-I don't know.
但听起来可不像是好消息啊
But does that sound like good news to you?
我还是从后门走为上策
I'm gonna slip out the back.
听起来就跟
Sounds like you were
你靠后门从墨西哥溜回来一样
slipping it out the back in Mexico, Frank.
你就是那个带着婴儿的妞
Wait, you're the chick with the baby?
Kev是不会让我6点之后再进去的
Kev won't let me in after 6:00 PM anymore.
Liam到底出什么鸟事儿了
What the hell's wrong with Liam?
-不是Liam  是Hymie  -靠
- This isn't Liam, it's Hymie. - Well, jeez.
让他别叫唤了
Shut him up.
Sheila生了个亚洲孩子
Sheila has an oriental baby?
我必须写完我的内战的作业
I have to finish my Civil War project...
-天呐  -他怎么一直哭呢
- Jesus. - ...and he won't stop crying.
你对Liam挺有办法的
You were always so good with Liam.
把他给我
Give-- give him--give him to me.
弄开他的嘴
Open his mouth.
-这是啥啊  -安定
- What is that? - Valium.
你不是要给孩子喂安眠药吧
Are you supposed to give Valium to a baby?
是 反正对你很有用
Oh, yeah. It always worked with you.
嘿
Oh.
瞧
Voila.
老爹谢谢
Thanks, daddy.
借我20块 行吧
Hey, loan me 20 bucks, will ya?
只有5块
I only have five.
够了
That'll do it.
我恨你
I hate you!
♪ Come, come, baby, yeah ♪
♪ come, come, baby, yeah ♪
♪ push my button,
make me wanna play ♪
你朋友很爱跳舞啊
Your friend likes to dance.
酒喝多了就这样
The tequila likes to dance.
你觉得你能
So you think you're gonna be able
弄好明晚的场子么
to pull this off tomorrow night?
希望能
Hope so.
我觉得你可以的
I bet you will
看起来你有些天赋的
Looks like you have some real talent.
你好像不是在说我搞定俱乐部的才能吧
You're not talking about my club promoting skills, are you?
为啥这么说
What makes you say that?
你的手放在我膝盖上
Your hand on my knee.
我还打算伸进你裙子里呢
I meant to put it up your skirt.
你觉得我拿到
What are the chances of me
你的联系名单的可能性大吗
getting ahold of your email lists?
我凭什么给你
Why would I give them to you?
额 帮助一个好人的满足感
Mm, satisfaction of knowing you're helping a good person.
不 我不会满足的
No, I can't come inside that.
我会分你好处的
I could give you a cut of my bar, then.
10%
10%?
你知道我花了多久才建好我的顾客名单的
You know how long it took me to build up my list?
你天真地认为我会冒险为了你的烂场子
You honestly think I'd risk it on you throwing some lame party
搞臭我的牌子而只因为少于50%的好处吗
and ruining my brand for anything less than 50%?
这是个有趣的建议
Well, that's an interesting offer.
等我和我姐妹商量下
Let me discuss it with my partner.
♪ Come, come, baby, yeah,
come, come, baby, yeah ♪
他说他的联系人名单值一半
He wants 50% of the bar for his email list,
这个傻逼
and he's a giant douche bag.
不用担心
No worries.
我从他的夹克里顺来了他的电话
I swiped his phone from his jacket
趁他的的手在你腿上的时候
as soon as I saw his hand on your knee.
可以搞定所有的联系人了
Has all his contacts.
敢想敢做对吧
Gotta be entrepreneurial, right?
-哈  -哈哈
- Aah! - Aah!
-Debbie  -晚安 Hymie
- Debbie? - Nighty-night, Hymie.
我的天呐
Oh, my goodness.
你怎么做到的 Debbie
How did you do it, Debbie?
我爸对孩子有一套
Daddy's good with babies.
你这是刚回来
You just getting home?
还没睡啊
Oh, hey. Still awake?
去哪了
Where have you been?
急诊室  被门挤了
Uh, Emergency Room. Slammed it in the door.
-额  -你有麻烦了
- Yeah. - Well, you're in trouble.
你让Carl在上学的日子熬夜
You let Carl stay up late on a school night.
我觉得你该打屁屁了
I think you need a spanking.
但是你穿着裤子我没法动手
I can't do it with your pants on, though.
那我就该脱了对吧
Then I should take them off.
坏男孩
Very bad boy.
我是个坏透了的男孩
I've been a bad, bad boy.
坏到家了
Bad.
普渡大学看起来棒极了
This Purdue place looks cool.
她肯定挣不回来
There's no way she's gonna
交财产税的钱
make the money back for the property tax.
上面说这是顶尖的
Says they're one of the top
工程类学校之一
engineering schools in the country.
我要想办法赚回来
I'm gonna have to figure out a way
她弄走的那1000块
to make up the 1,000 bucks she's gonna lose.
你在听我说话吗
You listening to me?
你知道的  走廊那头的激情戏
Yeah, you know, it's kind of hard
让我没法专心听你说话
with the, uh, porno going on across the hall.
我是因为听到这个才想干的  是不会有点怪呢
Is it wrong that it's kind of turning me on?
一点也不 我也这感觉
Yeah, me too.
-早安  - 早安
- Morning. - Hey.
Jimmy下来给我们做早餐吗
Jimmy gonna come down to make us breakfast?
他在睡呢 你们吃麦片吧
He's sleeping in. Eat your cereal.
-你把他榨干了吧  -你也是吃你的麦片
- Wore him out, huh? - You too. Eat your cereal.
已经坏了 来个煎蛋
Spoiled now. Need an omelet.
晚上的俱乐部怎么样了
So, um, how's the club night thing coming?
一定大获成功
Gonna be a big success.
也许赚够了钱再弄一个
Probably make enough money to roll it into another one.
借点小钱 生意就搞起来了
Take out a small loan, really get things going.
怎么了 Debs
What's wrong, Debs?
回来晚了
Got home late.
昨天晚上当婴儿保姆来的
Baby-sitting.
屌丝女孩
So the ghetto girl
认为她能活在美国梦里
thinks she can live the American dream, huh?
也许这次是我的机会 Lip
Maybe it's my time, Lip.
这事和你没关系 Mandy
None of your business, Mandy.
你还不明白么 那样行不通的 大姐
Don't you see, it doesn't work like that, sis.
当你没钱的时候 唯一赚钱的法子
When you're poor, only way to make money
不是偷就是骗
is to steal it or scam it,
就像 Don King和Joe Kennedy一样
like Don King or Joe Kennedy.
老爸回家了
Daddy's home!
-还有朋友  
- Brought friends. 
-没关系  -那是我的车子
- Just dump it. - Hey, that's my bike!
不能用了
Doesn't really work anymore.
因为你弄弯了车圈
Yeah, because you bent the rim, Frank.
还有车座呢
And where's the seat?
原来如此 怪不得我骑得时候那么疼
That's why it hurt so much when I rode it.
来吧 伙计们
Come on, fellas.
搞点吃的 喝点酒
Get some brekkie, soak up the alcohol.
-你有酵母吗  -这是我们的吃的
- Do you have sourdough? - Hey, this is our food!
别没礼貌
Don't be rude.
是因为钱吗 Fiona
Is this about money, Fiona?
我会很高兴付我那份的
Because I am happy to pay my share.
这就是你想尽一切方式从我身上得到的
That's all you ever want from me anymore anyway.
就在这 高兴了
There. You happy, huh?
这值300块呢
That's about $300 worth.
来吧 伙计们
Come on, lads!
上楼去 搞点迪斯科小憩
Let's go upstairs, take a disco nap
直到Alibi开门
till the Alibi's open again.
老爹 不要这样
Dad, no, no.
-Lip 不要  -这是我的家
- Lip, don't. - This is my home.
你没资格把我赶出去
You have no right to kick me out of it.
我是这儿重要的一员
I am an important part of this family.
你不是
No, you're not.
你不在这住了
You don't live here anymore.
好
Fine.
如果这是你想要的结果 我走
If that's the way you want it, I'll leave.
Phil Chester 对不住了
Phil, Chester, I'm sorry.
我家人不想我在这儿
My family doesn't want me here anymore.
冲
Charge!
混蛋
Jackass!
我受够了 我们上
That's it. Let's go! Go!
别让他们嚣张
Stop it, guys! Stop!
赶紧找张床 伙计们 找张床
Just pick a bed, fellas! Just pick a bed. Oh, my God!
你他妈的在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
快他妈的滚出去
Get the fuck outta here!
你不能睡这儿
Come. You are not sleeping here.
-不要这样  -起来
- No, stop! - Come on.
快起来
Get up, get up!
他没做错什么
He's not doing anything!
你不能
You are not going to--
-滚  -你发什么神经
- Go! - What's the matter with you?
反正也是一堆破烂儿
Well, that's a piece of shit anyway.
见鬼了 Frank 快滚
Damn it, Frank, get the fuck out!
你不能这么对她
No, you cannot do this to her!
-快起来  -老天 这是
- Come on! Get up right now! - Jesus! What's the--
-快滚  -滚
- Get out! - Get out!
别打了
Stop!
-我对你那么好  -你却
I treated you well! And you--
-啊哦  -你怎么能那么对我
- Ow! - How could you do this to me?
别打了
Stop! Stop--
滚出我的房子 我恨你
Get out of my house! I hate you!
-我甚至都不介意  -天呐
- I don't even care! - Jesus!
滚出去 滚
Get out! Get out!
爸
Dad.
把他弄出去  -我的天呐
- Get him out. - Ow, God!
滚出去
Get out!
我恨你
I hate you! Get--
能别碰我吗
don't you touch me!
上帝
Oh, my God.
滚
Get out!
我为你们付出那么多
After everything I have done for you,
这就是我得到的谢谢吗
this is the thanks I get.
-我们把他扔哪  -该去哪去哪
- Where should we put him? - Where he belongs.
-打开 Carl  -好的
- Open it up, Carl! - Got it.
无论你们
Whatever, you--
老天爷
Jesus Christ!
这不好玩 真的不好玩
Not funny! Not funny at all!
需要你们清理飞溅在墙上的血水
Gonna need you to clean the blood splatter on the walls,
地板上证据标记 然后修补弹孔
evidence marks on the floor, and patch up the bullet holes.
你们先从这些入手
That should get you started.
-工具在里面  -我擦
- Supplies are inside. - Shit.
咋啦 哥们
You okay, buddy?
花了一早上想弄一张
Been trying all morning to get tickets
今晚在Soldier广场的Wilco音乐会的票
to the Wilco concert at Soldier Field tonight.
- 结果没买上  -Wilco（乐队）
- Can't get through. - Wilco?
不就是那种头发梳到后发际线的大叔们
Aren't they for, like, dads with receding hairlines and shit?
算了吧 Wilco是那种反商业性质的
Come on, Wilco is the beacon of anti-commercialism.
好吧 因为没人愿意为那无聊的音乐花钱
Yeah, because no one wants to buy their whiny music,
所以他们才免费的
they gotta give it away for free.
我擦
Shit.
欧了 这是你的 除了之前50块
All right, here you go. It's 50 bucks a head.
这是400块
That's $400.
我有幸知道接下来几天的计划吗
is there any chance I can get an advance on the next couple days?
不要急 孩子
Hey, slow your roll, kid.
我还没看到他们能不能干
I haven't seen what they could do yet.
-先生  - 恩
- Señor. - Yeah?
这就是抢我们饭碗的人
This man stole our jobs?
不 我可没抢  只是我的价格更低
No, no, I didn't steal them, I just underbid you.
我们是非法移民 你怎么可能比我们还低
But we are illegal immigrants. How can you underbid us?
白人苦力就是新的社会底层
Ghetto white's the new brown.
-啥  -新奴隶
- The what? - The new brown.
这不公平
This is unfair.
还活在美国梦里呢 哥们儿
Just living the American dream, amigo!
好 我们先放8箱啤酒在前面
Okay, let's keep eight cases of that beer up front,
剩下的放在后面的冰箱里
and put the rest in the back refrigerator.
你好
Hello.
已经有人来了
People showing up already?
? Turn it up, turn it off now ?
- ? turn it up... ?
有什么需要帮忙的吗
- Can I help you?
Alderman Edward Gretsky,第十五任保卫
Alderman Edward Gretsky,
15th Ward.
好的
Okay.
开派对啊
Throwing a party, I see.
差不多
Something like that.
就是个善意的探访
Just a friendly visit.
确保你填好申请了
You know, make sure you filled
out all your applications.
什么申请
Applications?
营业执照，酒水执照，责任保险
Business license, liquor
license, umbrella insurance.
我确定Meg已经处理好你所需要的
Well, I'm sure Meg handled
everything that you need.
她确实是 但是是为她自己的生意
She did.
For her business.
什么
What?
你现在管秀场，对吧
Well, you're running
the show now, right?
是，但就今晚
Well, just for tonight.
那就今晚
Then just for tonight
我破个例，申请一个小额的申请费
I'll make an exception
on the applications for...
small filing fee.
申请费
就1000刀吧
- A filing fee?
- Let's say $1,000.
总不希望多事的警察和消防员
Wouldn't want
any pesky policemen or firemen
今晚出现吧，是吧
showing up now, would we?
我迟点来收
I'll come back later
to collect.
早上2点吧
Let's say 2:00 AM.
小指头怎么样了
How is the pinky?
还行
It's doing okay.
听着，我女朋友今晚要开一个party
So listen, my girlfriend's
having a party tonight.
我必须得露面
It's important that I go.
那肯定得有酒吧
Is there going to be
alcohol there?
这是个party，那肯定得有啊
It's a party, it's kind of
how these things work, yeah.
大麻呢
可能有
- Drugs?
- Maybe.
可能会出事
也许会也许不会
- Bad things may happen.
- Yeah, or not.
那我跟你一起去，以防万一
I go with you.
Just to make sure.
事情就是你不能跟我一起去
Yeah, see, that's the thing
is that you can't go with me
因为你去我就得解释你是谁
because then I'll have
to explain who you are,
我怎么认识你的，我的生活现在很危险
how I know you,
that my life's in danger.
我的意思是这事肯定不会很顺
I mean, that won't
go over very well.
那你就老实呆在家
Then you stay home.
Hey, Sanchez.
该还账了
- Aw, hell.
- Time to pay up.
他们放你出来了
表现的好
- They let you out?
- Good behavior.
我还以为有4个月呢
I thought I had
four more months.
重新想想
Think again.
学校的巡警过来了
Hey, yo,
campus security is coming.
你干什么呢
The hell are you doing?
不想你又被逮进去
Didn't want you to get busted.
我可以自己照顾自己，谢谢
I can look after myself,
thank you.
他和你在一起时，眼里有那种眼神吗
Does he get that look
in his eye-- look in his eye--
look in his eye
when he's with you?
刚出少管所，记得吗
Just got outta juvie, remember?
你他妈看什么呢
没什么
- The fuck are you looking at?
- Nothing.
你看上去真美
You look great.
谢谢，Debs
Thanks, Debs.
早上Frank的事，你还好吧
You okay with what happened
this morning? Frank?
jimmy在浴室呕吐呢
Jimmy's in the bathroom puking.
怎么了
What's going on?
我吃坏肚子了
Something I ate.
It's not sitting well.
你需要什么吗
You need anything?
我就肚子有点难受，今晚估计去不了
No, I'm just bummed
I can't make it tonight.
我真的很想去的
I mean, I really wanted to go.
如果你觉得迟点好受了，再去吧，好吗
If you feel better later,
come on over, okay?
好的
Okay.
走开，我们什么都不买
Go away. We're not buying.
老天啊
Jeez.
我知道，你想让我找到上帝
I know, I know,
you want me to find Jesus.
我已经找到上帝了，谢谢
I already found him, thanks.
我要找Kev
I'm looking for Kev.
Kevin Ball.
我是他老婆
I'm his wife.
? I ask myself why
but I don't know ?
? fairy tales... ?
Tommy!
你的车库还在吗
Hey, you still got that garage?
是的，Frank，和我的房子是配套的
Yeah, it kinda
comes with the house, Frank.
好的，你觉得让我睡你车库怎么样
Great. What's say
you let me sleep there?
做梦
What's say I don't.
为什么不行呢
因为上次
- Why the hell not?
- Because the last time
你呆在我这，你在我厨房水槽尿尿
you stayed at my place,
you shit in my kitchen sink.
那是因为你家的布局太让人困惑了
The layout of your home
is very confusing.
不行，Frank
No, Frank.
不行就是不行
No means no.
操你，Tommy
Fuck you, Tommy.
操你就是操你
Fuck you means fuck you.
Kermit!
我的好朋友
My best friend.
你不能住我那，Frank
You can't stay with me, Frank.
要是我给你口交呢
Wh-- what if
I suck your dick?
Frank.
要不你移民去墨西哥吧，怎么样Frank
What if you immigrate
to Mexico, Frank?
反转移民大潮
Reverse the prevailing tide.
你干嘛呆在这
Why are you even here?
难道你不应该去领残疾证吗
Should be
collecting disability.
因为我不是在工作时把脚摔断的
'Cause I didn't
injure my foot at work.
要不让我住你家吧
Hey, let me crash
at your place.
我告诉保险公司你是自己弄伤的
I'll tell the insurance company
that you did.
为什么你不能呆在你自己的地方呢，Frank
Why can't you stay
at your place, Frank?
就是那帮不知道感恩的小混蛋
Ungrateful little shits! That's why.
我为他们做了那么多
Things I do for them.
流血，流汗，还有流泪
Blood, sweat, and tears.
问明是一家人 他们不应该这么对我
This is not how a family
treats each other.
Yeah.
等会  找你的  V
Hang on.
It's for you. V.
嘿 亲爱的 什么事吗
Hey, baby, what's going on?
你说什么
What?
不会吧  好的
No, yeah, okay.
好的 我马上回去
Okay, I'll be right there.
帮我照看一会酒吧
Watch the bar.
那个红头发的贱人是最垃圾的一个 ( 指debbie )
Little redheaded bitch
is the worst of 'em.
其他人这么对我 我不奇怪
Expect it from the others,
but not from--
可我没想到
not from--
from...
没想到她  Debbie
her--
Debbie.
她那么好脾气竟然都这么对我
Orphan Annie turned on me.
我为什么受伤
That's how I got
all these bruises.
就是她打得我  用球拍打的我
She hit me.
With a bat.
现在 我连碰都碰不得她了
Now, I can't touch her.
No.
这完全就是孩子虐待我  我得向机关报告
That is child abuse.
I'd get reported.
接线员 你能帮我接儿童福利
Operator, can you connect me
with Child Welfare Ser--
儿童福利机构吗
Services?
你好 我想举报个事
Yes, hello.
I would like to report, uh...
一个家长丢弃孩子
a-a negligence situation.
2119 North Wallace.
Gallagher家
Gallagher.
六个生活困苦的孩子
Six kids living in squalor.
他们没有父母抚养
No parental supervision.
爸爸在的时候  也是喝醉了的
When the father is there,
he's drunk.
他还打孩子
He hits them.
不  他们不配
Not-- n-not that they
don't deserve it.
他们也全都不是好孩子
They're all criminals,
delinquents, viol-- What?
算了吧 我不想说我是谁
No, if it's all right, I would
like to remain anonymous.
没事  谢谢你
No, thank you.
上帝保佑你
And God bless you.
你竟然能干出这样的事来
That is an all-time low.
Frank  没想到你能垃圾到这个地步
Even for you, Frank.
♪ charge amex, see ♪
♪ like you got an "A,"
score credit ♪
♪ living that American dream ♪
♪ you could be a celebrity ♪
♪ when you step on the scene ♪
♪ I know you gotta look hot ♪
♪ you and your girls
with dresses ♪
♪ turn that sound up ♪
♪ you are in the limelight ♪
♪ until they cut
your power out ♪
♪ shopping like a rich girl ♪
♪ rich girl, like a rich girl ♪
嘿 v  你在哪呢
Hey, V, where are you?
这个地方嗨极了  我们成功了
This place is insane!
We did it!
♪ like a rich girl ♪
♪ credit card, max it out ♪
Wilco的秘密音乐会在哪
where Wilco's gonna play
a secret concert?
好的 它在
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's, uh,
20刀  你自己停车  30刀 我们帮你停
20 bucks, self-parked.
30 valet.
- 我自己停车吧 -没问题
- I'll park it myself.
- Cool.
你把车开到那边
Uh, just pull over
right down there.
那边有个小妞会告诉你怎么走
That lovely lady
will show you to your spot.
-谢了 -没问题 祝你玩的开心
- Thank you.
- Cool. Have fun.
- Yo.
- Hey, Lip.
忙什么呢 兄弟
How you doing, man?
不错 收到你的那个Wilco音乐会的短信了
Good. Got your text about
the impromptu Wilco concert.
我tweeter所有我认识的人了
Tweeted everyone I know.
我猜到了
Thought you might.
你出来吧  我找个人帮你停车
Hey, hop out. I'll have someone park your car.
-谢谢  -乐意效劳。
- Thanks. - Cool.
我们要做多久？
How long we doing this for?
还有30多辆要停
Figure we park about 30 more cars,
够交房产税吗？
make enough money to cover the property tax,
合适那些傻逼才知道Wilco（著名独立摇滚乐队）
at which time people will probably start to realize
不在Fiona的夜店
Wilco's not playing at Fiona's club.
我们还是快逃
Then we bolt.
吧
Out.
我没地方可去
Where am I supposed to go?
摇摇他
Just-- just shake him.
你不应该摇婴儿
You're not supposed to shake a baby.
我知道 我只想让他别再哭了
I know, but maybe it'll make him stop crying.
当然 他脑子摇坏了当让就不哭了
Yeah, because his brains will get scrambled.
他的脑子可以已经坏掉了。
- They already are!
摇一摇可能把
I'm just saying maybe it'll
他的脑子又摇好了
scramble 'em back together again.
老相识 最近怎么样
Howdy, folks.
你需要人照顾他吧
You need help with that baby?
你怎么进来的
- How'd you get in my house?
我还留着钥匙。
I still have a key.
我有个提议
I-I-I got a proposition for you, Sheila.
-什么 不   -Frank你必须离开
- What? No! - Frank, you have to leave.
不 让我留下 我做你们的保姆
No, let me stay, and I'll be your wet nurse.
只是别让他吸我的奶奶就成
I don't mean your wet nurse,
that involves breast-feeding,
我可以做你的保姆 你孩子的保姆
but your nurse, your baby nurse.
只要给我提供食宿 你就会有八小时的睡眠
Room and board, you'll get eight hours of sleep a night.
我保证
I can promise you that.
Debbie是说他很擅长照顾婴儿
Debbie did say he was good with babies.
看？我已声名远扬了。
There, you see? My reputation precedes me.
给我五分钟
Just give me five minutes.
好吧，就30秒
Aw, hell. Give me 30 seconds.
如果我不能把他弄入睡
If I can't put this little tyke to sleep,
我就离开，我保证
I'll-- I'll leave, pronto.
来抱抱
I got you.
我自己带大8个孩子
Raised eight kids myself.
我知道怎么做
I know what I'm doing.
好了好了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们来
Here you go.
你怎么做到的 Frank
how did you do that, Frank?
上床前我想我得冲个澡
I think I'll take a shower before bed.
75, 76, 78.
好，正好过1万
Okay. Just over 10 grand.
不错呀
That's not bad.
你的15%
So, 15% for you.
我想咱们定好的是20
I thought we agreed on 20.
对
Right.
$2,000.
谢了
Thank you.
你什么时候给我都行
Take mine anytime you're ready.
期待下次合作愉快
Look forward to doing business with you in the future.
这些付酒钱
This is to cover my booze.
还剩2000是我的
And that leaves me with 2 grand.
没忘了我们吧
Didn't forget about us, did you?
当然没有
Of course not.
谢谢 Fiona
Thanks, Fiona.
♪ Do you want my love, boy ♪
- ? do you want my love ?
- Five, six, seven, eight...
$900?
这是我全部剩下的
That's all I have left?
你第一次已经不错了
That's not bad for your first gig.
但这还合不上我押金呢
But that doesn't even cover my deposit.
今晚上赔了100
I lost $100 doing this night.
还以为你要赔更多呢
Surprised you didn't lose more.
我办了8场演唱会才开始赚钱
It took me, like, eight gigs before I saw a profit.
这钱是你应该花的
You gotta pay your dues.
♪ do you want my love ♪
怎么样
What's going on?
我今晚能在这睡吗
Can I sleep here tonight?
当然
Sure.
怎么样
How'd you do?
离我开始赚钱还要一阵子
It's gonna take a while till I start making money.
拿着 差不多全部了
Here. Almost all of it.
我会补上剩下的 我保证
I'll get the rest, I promise.
-留着吧  -什么
- Ah, keep it. - What?
如果你拿我们的钱去赌
Well, if you're gonna gamble our money,
你也得坚持下去吧
you should hold onto it, right?
我本来是想改善咱们的生活 Lip
I was trying to better our situation, Lip.
那祝贺你了
Oh, congratulations.
你把所有都赌上，结果还没保本
You risked everything, and you didn't even break even.
这是我第一次做
It was my first time doing this.
这不是重点
That's not the point.
你问也不问我们 就自己做决定
You made a decision without consulting the rest of us.
-这个家是我负责的  -真的么
- I'm in charge of this family. - Really?
对不起 我第一次听说
No, I'm sorry, that's-- that's news to me.
你看着的 Fiona 如果我们每个人都只想自己
You see, Fiona, if we're gonna be every man for himself,
那这个家很快就完蛋了
this family is going under fast.
把钱拿着 好吧
Here, just take the money, okay?
把房产税交了 我明天怎么也把剩下的补上
Pay the property tax. I'll get the rest tomorrow somehow.
我不需要
No, I don't need it.
什么
What?
我自己对现状负责任
I took care of the situation myself.
怎么付
How?
跟北边那些孩子们说
Told a bunch of North Side kids
Wilco乐队去了你的夜店
that Wilco was playing at your party.
就像我说的
It's like I said.
当你穷的时候唯一赚钱方法
The only way to make money when you're poor
就是偷或者骗
is to steal it or scam it.
要是不用这么赚钱了 记得告诉我哈
But hey, um, let me know if the rules are changing, right,
还是你准备继续这么干呢
and you're gonna pull this shit again?
或者我来接管家里的钱
Maybe I'll have to take over the family money, huh?
你确定吗
Are we sure about this?
他带大了6个好孩子
He raised six great kids.
你看他呀
Look at him.
他就像能和宝宝对话一样
He's like the baby whisperer.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com